Right, you also worked on general insurance company ICICI Lombard, so
good, wonderful,
keep updating the data like this, right, it will give
you confidence. The
general insurance data that I shared with you here,
look, I shared two things
with you, one is ICC General data, but friends, the
question should be why not ICC General, second,
General Insurance, right? Secondly,
how many general insurance companies, why not all of them,
so I
also shared the analysis of general insurance with you, right, how is the
growth of general insurance, which
company is growing how much, now like
IC Lombard is number one in market share,
excluding private government companies,
because there is not going to be growth in government companies,
right, so in private, ICC Lombard, Bajaj Finance,
now Bajaj Finance means friends, is this a
part of Bajaj Finance or a part of Bajaj Finance,
tell me what do I mean by Bajaj Finance, Bajaj
Finance Life and Bajaj Alliance
General are part of Bajaj Finance and they are
part of Bajaj Finance, now this thing should be
clear, right, Bajaj Finance is only a finance
company, but Bajaj Finance when  You take it, it
means that there is Bajaj Finance as well, there is Bajaj Life as well, there is
Bajaj General as well and there is one good thing which
I will tell you after some time, right
when I will come to that topic, I mean while you should
understand that Bajaj is doing good, right it is at second place,
not bad, but we have
invested in ACC Lombard, right because it
is an independently listed company and anyway it is a
good company, they have high market share,
they are well profit making, right,
like many companies are still making
losses in general insurance, ICICI
Lombard is consistently making profit,
so I have given many more data as well, you can see at
your own time, see, I have
copied the data of all the companies here, from
where I took it from IRDA, right, so you can
know the market share of each company, right,
ICICI General, when I came, or right,
Bankim Bhai, you have written correctly, Bajaj Finance, right,
so when I
came to the data of ICICI General, till last year, friends, last
year was such a year, last in fact, I would say during the time of
Covid, what happened in the time of Covid, what was the
growth here  The profits were not increasing
because there were a lot of claims. What will happen with
this? Friends, if there are a lot of claims, then
their profits will
fall. So, we had seen their challenging times a little during the
time of Covid, right, you
can see that there was a profit of 1400 crores and 1200 crores, but
why was this profit made? You know,
I had told you about a combination ratio,
combination ratio, that is, how much premium do I
pay? This is the combined ratio. I
paid a premium of Rs 100, Rs. 100 and claims of Rs. 100 came,
premium of Rs. 100 and the expenses incurred in bringing the premium were
Rs. 100 and claims of Rs. 100 came, so the
combined ratio is Rs. Now, if the premium
comes to Rs. 100 and claims of Rs. 90 came, and if you add all the expenses together, the total comes to
90, then it is very favourable for me.
This premium will be used
in investment. Right, and general
insurance companies are investors;
they do not have the right to
distribute the entire profit, that is why you will
always see investment income in their results.
Life insurance companies are big investors, they have a
huge investment
income, but general is also not less,
friends, you can imagine the profit,
almost that much investment income is coming,
so you will say Piyush bhai, as many
claims will come as premium, so from where will he make profit,
brother, investment income is also
giving profit, right, so
how will we know in advance from the combined ratio, now the
combined ratio is 103 right now, it was 108 during the
time of Covid, it is decreasing, that means it is
favorable, right, that is why ICC Lombard was
in bad correction, you can see, profits were
not increasing, right, demand was good, 19
17, that means good demand, but profits were
not good, but from the last few quarters, profits have
increased again, friends, the results of quarter four that have come are
amazing, the more the premium increased in quarter four, the more the
profit increased, we
wanted that your profits should also be
comparable, that no problem,
ICICI Lombard has not done well since the time of Covid,
brother, now it is your turn,
what did I expect  I have just made my estimate from 18 of this year for
next year
because premiums are going well.
Look at quarter four also, in quarter four the
premiums are bigger than 17. This is an improvement, is
n't it from the month? So my expectation is 18. Now
what do you think, should I expect growth of 5 at this time? No, if
I keep 30 then it is the
same, no. So let's always go
with the trend. I have expected margins at 18 to be
8.3 and my profits to grow by 31
this year. According to this, if I
look at my P, I
will see profit growth at 31 this year and the PE is only 33,
so the PEG ratio is absolutely favorable. The more the
PE, the more growth we can expect in such companies. Yes, a
rally should come here.
This year I expect that the ICC
premium will reach 30,000 crores and
their profit will be 2500 crores. EPS of 51,
fair value 153, so yes, the evil that
was there till now has now come out for the first time in a
long time.  And the improvement we saw from here for the last nine
months, you will see that
in the chart as well. See what the chart
says for ACC Lombard. I open at this. I went to
ICICI Lombard
stock. This is IC Lombard General
Insurance. Friends, when the company's IPO came,
it was something like this. There are no charts then.
Based on past data, we had expected
that we would get good growth in this company.
We will see that premiums will increase,
profits will increase and our reserves will increase. And see,
after 2018, premium of Rs 12000 crore to Rs
25000 crore, we saw premiums increasing,
profits increasing, rate reserves increasing.
And that is why we saw this effect in the chart as well.
Whenever the rate falls, do not worry.
See, when their IPO came, after the IPO, the rate came from 6 to
872 or in some four-month period.
Then which candle was formed? This candle is this or
can I see this bullish angle finger candle which will further increase the
stock and I should see this is a
doji candle and I can see  What is this written, let
me see it first, Bankim bhai, shooting
star, okay, near, near, we can say this, Bankim
bhai, this is an inverted hammer, selling pressure has come from above,
right, inverted hammer, Herschel,
you have written it absolutely right, so what happened in an inverted hammer,
in an inverted hammer,
selling pressure has come from above, but there is no problem with it
until it does not go below the low, and
after that we saw a low being formed, there is no tension, so what
happened after that, there was a correction for three-four
months, right, then what
after 2018, we saw the stock moving again, and from
2018, till where did we see the rally,
from 700 to 1400, it doubled, from 2018 to 2019, one year,
friends, those who were bored here, oh friend
sir, it does not move, it does not move, what is it to them, there is
excitement every day, now
excitement will come in the picture every day, this is
not a comedy film which will give
you excitement, right, this is an investment which will
run very peacefully, those who got bored and left here  He
said, "This isn't working right now.
I'll take another one." He left from here and
went to another one, and it started moving. Then, when this one starts moving, it
comes here. After that, it goes back into a sharp
correction. Then, what happened? The
Covid pandemic caused tremendous claims.
Friends, we saw ICC Lombard in a long
correction. How long a correction?
Friends, you guys saw it. Right, a long
correction. As profits rose again, there was a hope
that yes, our profits will increase. The stock
recovered, and this stock is preparing to move back from here, continuing just
as it had moved here.
Friends, I
can expect that as
profits increase here,
we will see it rally again for another two or three years.
Right, keep one negative thing in
mind. The IMD has said that the rains will be
good, so this is positive for rural areas.
This also increases demand. But in some places, there will be
heavy rains. If there are floods in some places, then
claims also increase in such a situation.
Right, all these things are considered. So,
why were we expecting a rally here?
We were expecting it in advance
because  Improvement friends,
when the improvement will deteriorate, when there will be no improvement, then
this stock will fall, so this chart does not tell whether it will
run or run, who tells this, it is
decided by the business whether I will run or I will
fall, so yes I am
expecting a good rally from here, now till
when will this rally go, friends, overall I can expect
growth from the general insurance company at 13,
long term 13 14 15, all this
is conservative, friends, in other
developed countries, friends, in those countries, like
our annual income is two lakhs, but why do
people of developed economies pay a premium of two lakhs annually,
because there is money, people
want safety, so yes we will see here also
in the coming times, friends,
two things to be positive, one is that a lot of vehicles are being sold right now, so these
two wheeler, four
wheeler commercial vehicles will also be sold, these
vehicles will be sold, this will also increase their motor
insurance and the government is targeting
insurance for all, in the coming times the
government wants  That every person should be
insured, right, this is also beneficial for them.
I would hope friends,
by 2030, the premium pay will reach Rs 50,000 crore. But
such a small
estimate of 2030 is not equal. Friends, the estimates should be of minimum 10 years. I
remember we used to keep the target of 2017.
When we used to take this estimate in 2007, then
when I used to see this figure of different companies, I used to think,
oh, will it really be so big in 2017? Is it
possible that the business will grow so much, the
profits will increase so much? So today that
story has become so big, the business of every company,
both sales and profits and the prices are also
big. Friends, we have seen companies worth thousands of
rupees, friends, their value has become 10, 15,
but if I say the truth, I was not confident.
I made this after learning from Buffet.
In his book, Buffet Way,
he has told this. So I started making it,
but I did not have the confidence.
Sir, he used to say  This happens, that happens, let's
see when all these
years started passing in front of our eyes, he started learning how
sales increase, how profits increase, right, but
minimum 10 years because
anything can go wrong in 10 years, three years can go wrong, if
something else happens then so an
estimation below 10 years can lead you wrong, a 10
year estimation will always take you on the right path
because even if something goes wrong in between,
it gets taken off, right, so year we are
expecting lakh crore premium in
2035, right today friends, there are China Singapore
companies whose premium is two lakh crore each in
life insurance, general insurance, right, the
same thing will happen in India too,
where is there a shortage of people, there are 150 crore people,
my fair valuation itself will be around 5000, so will the
share price be ten thousand or not, so
you should see this in the chart, if it
is 1700 today, you should know that it is going to run
from here, but you should think that it should continue
straight to 1700  If you earn Rs. 10,000 or 5,000 from this, it wo
n't happen, it will work again for two or three
years, some problem will arise, then it will work again for
two or three years, it will deteriorate while doing this,
if you earn Rs. 10,000, what is the
problem for us, right, no problem, you can keep doing it like this, but
what is the benefit for us, that with this
we will also get dividends every year, we will keep
earning, the time will come when the amount of
money we invested will come in dividend,
and the more mature the company becomes,
friends, this year HDFC MC gave a dividend of 77,
mind blowing, at
77, that means it distributed 7% of the profit,
it cannot do it normally because
it has expenses, MC company does
not have any expenses, it has a high rate, but this
will also mature in a year, friends, this will also
give you a good dividend, now tell me there is no worry, you do
n't want dividend, you just run around like this,
friends, investments are made for a long time,
now you can do this investment in any company,
you can do it in Star Health, you
can do it in New India, but  Friends,
how can you predict the future for those whose past is not consistent? Half the life of a star has been spent
in losses. Now you will say that he will
run, he will run, he is going to run. Why?
Because not Star Health, General Insurance is going to
run. General Insurance is going to become
big. But you
need consistency, so friends, not every company will provide that.
We are not traders. Today, we took the one that surpassed the moving
average, tomorrow it
broke out, we took that. I have been meeting traders for
15 years, friends. They bring new companies every year, they do
not earn in any of them, they do
well, they are technically good and strong,
but friends, they do not create wealth.
Right, after 10-15 years, they think, oh friend,
I had this stock once upon a time, but what is the use of that stock
today? It is
not there today because
you sold it and bought another company. You should not
do this, friends, diversify
in different sectors and focus on that.
In the same company, friends,
increase your weightage. When bad times come, when the stock does
not do well, do not abandon the boat and run. When
bad times come, only then  If the stock falls, then only
your quantity will increase. Look,
if ICC General Insurance continued, then
we would not have accumulated stock.
This did not work, that is why we got it at a lower price.
Whoever bought here also got an XY fixed
dividend. Whoever bought here also got an XY
fixed dividend. Who benefited the most, who bought during the fall? So
friends, during the fall, keep an eye on the companies because
you get good returns at that time. I am seeing a big
buying from the lower level.
Which candle has formed as we
saw? But an inverted hammer.
Can you also say something like a hammer? What happened this month? It
fell strongly here till here. Then something happened that
buying came strongly from the bottom and this became its
permanent low. After this,
we did not see that low at any time. Amazing low right. Yes, pay
attention to the hammer when it falls.
Inverted hammer. Pay attention when it rallies.
Right now your share is moving.
We saw another good candle here.
Look, I drew a line here.
What did I do? Alt H.
Again Alt H Alt H means horizontal Alt
C means vertical, this is a vertical line, I do
n't need a vertical line either, so
I will delete the vertical line right now,
I need an empty Alt as horizontal line, right, if I do
n't want to trouble my eyes, I made a
little broad line, see it is clear
that it closed at a lifetime high, a
nice bullish angle finger candle was formed, this
bullish angle finger candle says that something has happened
in this month which did not happen in the last two years
and what has happened, again there are talks of lifetime
high premium, lifetime high profit, so that is why the
stock is running, it will
rest for two-three months, then
what does it have to run, right, so look at both the things,
friends, not an empty chart,
what is important with the chart, the result data, right,
fundamentals, friends, this was the
data of General Insurance